Negli episodi precedenti...
- Hai un compagno di stanza?
- No, è una singola.
Io ho uno chaperon.
Perché hai uno chaperon?
Magari credono che sia una combinaguai.
Visto che mi hai preso
a pugni in faccia, hanno ragione.
- Tu giochi a D&D?
- No,
sto sempre in camera a studiare
perché non ho amici.
- Che sfigata.
- Già.
Mi sa che vado.
Ciao.
Dovresti andarle dietro.
Perché? È una sfigata, l'hai detto tu.
ADULT SHELDON:
Many cultures
throughout the world
relied on percussion
to send messages
across long distances.
For example,
the West African dundun
was used to imitate
human speech...
(loud music playing)
...while I used my fist,
the wall of my dorm,
and Morse code
to send a message.
(four knocks)
That's just the letter "H."
What does that mean?
Yeah?
I'm here to talk to you
about your music
and your abysmal
Morse code skills.
What?
Four dots is just
the letter "H."
Was your message "Huh"?
What?
Paige?
Sheldon?
You know him?
Yeah, no,
we go way back.
What are you doing here?
Would you believe me
if I told you I was working on
a femtosecond laser
in the engineering department?
Yes.
Then that.
You know she's not old enough
to drink beer.
I'm not old enough
Yeah, one second.
Come here.
Did I convince you
that drinking is wrong?
Good for me.
Just leave me alone.
But what are you doing here?
I'm trying to have fun,
and I don't want them to know
how old I am.
Why?
Because I want them to think
that I'm cool.
But you're smart.
What's cooler than that?
Just go away.
Hey, we're fixing to play
some beer-pong. You in?
You should know,
she is not...
Not had dinner. I have
not had dinner yet, so
we are going
to go get some food.
We are?
Do you have cash?
Of course.
I always have
an emergency 20,
plus four quarters
for the telephone.
21 bucks?
Okay, you're buying.
We're going the wrong way.
Okay, well, I'm drunk.
You lead.
* Nobody else
is stronger than I am *
* Yesterday I moved a mountain *
* I bet I could be your hero *
* I am a mighty little man *
* I am a mighty little man. *
DINOSAUR (on TV):
Here, take a look at this.
Does this look like tuna to you?
(laughs)
What am I watching?
It's called Dinosaurs.
It's like The Flintstones,
only with dinosaurs. Come on.
Well, that's dumb.
Well, they talk, he's
got a job. It's fun.
Wasn't The Flintstones
just The Honeymooners?
Huh, I never even
thought about that.
Well, see, you just
kind of ruined it for me.
Good.
Hey.
Please tell me you brought
some movies home.
Tootsie.
Ooh, thank you.
Really? We're supposed
to believe
Dustin Hoffman is a woman?
But we believe
talking dinosaurs?
Okay, I'll leave you to it.
Little late
to start a movie.
It's 8:00.
We're saying the same thing.
So, you want to go home?
Well, I don't know.
I stayed here last night.
So?
So, two nights in a row.
At what point
are we living together?
Fine. Go home.
Oh, I'm okay with staying.
You're the independent one.
If you want to stay, stay.
If you want to go, go.
Fine. I'll stay
if you're gonna beg.
And this isn't what I wanted.
Are you still inebriated,
or can we have
an intelligent conversation?
Both.
You do realize that
alcohol kills brain cells.
Ah, but it also makes
life tolerable.
What do you mean?
Well, talking to you
is usually annoying.
So you're what's called
a mean drunk. Noted.
I'm messing with you.
It's just, sometimes
life sucks,
and it's easier
not to deal with it.
Could you be more specific?
Um... well, I
have no friends,
I don't fit in anywhere,
and I dropped out of college
but I'm too young
to get a job,
so killing brain cells
makes it easier.
Huh.
Go ahead, smart guy, fix me.
Mm.
Well, give me a minute.
(stammers)
* Sweet Tootsie roll... *
Well, how do they not see
that's Dustin Hoffman?
I buy it.
So if I put on
a wig and lipstick,
you'd think I was a chick?
(chuckles)
Only one way to find out.
Nice try.
You do have some pretty
nice legs, though.
Well, if you want,
we could pause the movie,
and I'll let you
touch 'em.
Lucky me.
So I'm assuming you haven't
taken the DARE pledge.
The what?
DARE. It's an acronym.
It stands for Drug Abuse
Resistance Education.
It's not too late.
You can take it now.
I promise not to do drugs,
to avoid violence,
to be responsible, and to
make responsible choices.
Now you say it.
No.
I dare you.
Clever, right?
Because I still have
all my brain cells.
Sheldon, just eat your pizza.
Hey. You guys going to a party?
Uh, Gamma Kappa house.
Cool.
Mm, you know,
Officer McDaniel was in charge
of our DARE program.
One time, he even brought in
his drug-sniffing dog Alfie.
Which I didn't care for,
but it was nice to see
a dog gainfully employed
and off the streets.
MEEMAW:
Really? You're gonna
leave your socks on?
DALE:
My feet get cold.
MEEMAW: Take 'em off.
DALE: What do you care?
MEEMAW:
It feels like
a lack of commitment.
DALE:
Aw, fine.
MEEMAW:
When was the last time
you cut your toenails?
DALE:
I don't know.
MEEMAW:
Seriously, you look
like something
that could swoop down
and pick up a squirrel.
(knock on door)
Look who's here. Come on in.
Thanks.
Everything okay?
Mind if I hang out here
with y'all?
Come on, mama.
(pats couch)
Need a break from Connie?
I'm just trying to give
her and Dale some privacy.
Gross.
Oh.
What?
Oh, nasty.
Wait, sex, right?
Yeah.
Missy's at a sleepover
if you want to use her room.
I might take
you up on that.
You'll be safe here.
They never do anything.
(rock music playing,
lively chatter)
What are we
doing here?
It's a party, Sheldon.
But we weren't invited.
I didn't bring a gift.
Then go home.
Wait, this is dangerous.
ADULT SHELDON:
There I stood,
the classic hero
outside the dragon's cave.
Should I risk life and limb
to save the maiden?
My every instinct said no.
But I drank a lot of root beer
and really had to go pee-pee.
* Let's go! *
(rock music playing,
lively chatter)
Hell does exist.
Excuse me. Where's
the nearest restroom?
Hey, look, Pee-wee
Herman's at our party!
ALL (chanting):
Pee-wee! Pee-wee! Pee-wee!
Pee-wee! Pee-wee!
The hell continues.
(toilet flushes)
Oh, thank goodness.
Come on!
Hey, there's a line.
Oh, boy. New hell.
(Dale cries out)
MEEMAW: What?!
What?!
Charley horse. Charley horse.
What-what do I do?
I don't know. (stammers)
Here, rub it,
rub it, rub it.
That's kind of how this whole
thing got started. (snickers)
That's not funny.
Mm-hmm.
You'll laugh later.
DALE:
Rub harder. Harder.
MEEMAW:
I'm rubbing as
hard as I can.
DALE:
Well, use your elbow.
MEEMAW: All right.
(Dale groaning)
I don't need my toothbrush.
MEEMAW:
You like that?
DALE:
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
ADULT SHELDON:
This night of depravity
had reduced me
to urinating on a tree
like a forest animal.
How much worse could it get?
PAUL:
Hey, Pee-wee's back!
ALL (chanting):
Pee-wee! Pee-wee! Pee-wee!
Pee-wee!
Excuse me.
I'm looking
for my friend.
Blonde girl,
about a meter and a half.
(rock music and lively chatter
continue)
* Suck the poison out... *
Excuse me. I'm looking for...
Missy?
Sheldon?
What are you doing here?
What are you
doing here?
Do Mom and Dad know
you're here?
Okay, stop. You go first.
Heather's sister
goes to school here.
She invited us.
Now you.
I'm looking after Paige.
Where is she?
Well, I didn't say
I was doing a great job.
Where's your toothbrush?
I don't want to talk about it.
(phone ringing)
Who the hell calls
at this hour?
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Everything okay?
Who is it?
Heather's mom.
Oh. Is everything okay?
You just heard me ask.
Wh-What's up?
No, Heather's not here.
They're at your house.
Huh.
What?
Heather told her mom
she was staying here.
(chuckles)
Classic.
Paige is drunk?
And high on what
Officer McDaniel's called
Mary Jane, reefer and ganja.
Is she okay?
No.
She said her life is terrible.
What?
Her life is terrible.
(rock music continues loudly)
(music stops)
Her life is terrible.
(crowd murmuring)
(muttering)
How's your sex
cramp, old man?
Athletes get cramps
all the time.
It comes from dehydration,
overexertion.
I'll give you
the dehydration,
but I didn't see any
overexertion, though.
Why, Connie?
'Cause it's fun.
Well, just give me
a minute, I'll be ready.
Why don't we just
call it a night
and get some sleep?
That's fine by me,
but just to be clear,
you're calling it,
not me.
Yep.
I'm good to go.
I'm sure you are.
Yep.
Damn tootin'. (groans)
I don't know if it's any
help, but when I was her age
and pulled this, it was
just to go to a party.
(scoffs)
Oh, great.
So she's at a party,
who knows where.
GEORGE SR.:
You know what?
I'm gonna go find her.
How?
I don't know. I'm just--
I'm gonna drive around
till I hear some carousing.
I'll go with you.
Will you both just
stop for a minute?
There's nothing to do but wait.
Fine.
Nope. Georgie, let's go.
Let's check out that
creek in the woods
where they found
the headless body.
GEORGE SR.:
Will you shut up.
(sighs)
Now what do we do?
We can't just leave.
Paige is still in there.
Maybe we should call Mom.
I do have four quarters
for that exact reason.
Paige?
Wait!
What are you doing?
Well, this is Bradley, and
we're going to another party.
Another party? It's 9:30.
Bradley, do you know
how old she is?
She said she was 18.
Lower.
Sixteen?
Okay, I got to go.
Thanks a lot.
Come on.
We're running again?
We just ran.
I'll tell you what.
My daughter's never gonna
put me through this.
Oh, really? How you figure?
I'm gonna run a tight ship.
Set some rules, some boundaries.
If she breaks them,
then she faces the...
Oh, what do you call it?
Repercussions.
(snickers)
Why you smiling?
I just can't wait
till you're a dad.
Thank you.
"Repercussions."
It's a word. Look it up.
(sighs)
MISSY:
Hurry!
This is as fast as I can go
in sensible shoes.
(Paige retching)
(groans)
You okay?
No.
Oh, dear.
What?
I'm going to have the
mother of all blisters.
(sighs)
I'm worried about you.
Thank you.
Well, don't be.
I'm having fun.
You're drunk
and you were about to get
in the car with some stranger.
So? He was cute.
What's wrong with you?
You're smarter than Sheldon.
Why don't you act like it?
Um...
I am.
If that was true, then how come
my pizza's still in my stomach
and yours is in the fountain?
(groans)
What good is being smart
if you're all alone?
Let's go to Sheldon's
so I can get you cleaned up.
(groans softly)
Thanks.
Just so you know,
you're not alone.
You've got me.
I thought we were trying
to make her feel better.
(music playing quietly
over radio)
I'll tell you another idea I
have for keeping my kid in line.
Oh, can't wait.
I seen this show
where they put
these electric trackers
on these dolphins.
And with satellites, they
can tell exactly where they are.
Dolphins?
Go on.
I'm gonna stick one
of them things in my kid
so I always know where she is.
So you're gonna keep track
of your daughter
like she's an animal.
Damn straight.
Actually a really good idea.
Missy's a good kid.
I'm sure she's okay.
(sighs)
I was a good kid.
Didn't stop me from
getting into trouble.
(chuckles) Me, too.
One time,
I was at this party and...
Actually, never mind.
The important thing is
we survived.
Yes, we did.
(inhales deeply)
You just want your children
to have an easier time of it.
Easier.
My baby's gonna have a broke
single mom and a teenage dad.
Mm-hmm.
Let me get you some more tea.
Okay.
You know what else is nice?
Hmm?
I get to learn from
all your parenting mistakes.
I'm starting to think
letting you live this
long was one of 'em.
Like that. I'd never say
something so awful to my kid.
(scoffs)
Thanks, big guy.
(crickets chirping)
You awake?
Mm-hmm.
I've been thinking.
We don't have to spend
every night together.
Wow.
You're preaching to the choir
there, Connie.
I've been lying awake here
for an hour,
wishing I were back home
in my own bed.
Really?
Everything's
the way I like it there.
Got a TV in the bedroom
and leave the seat up
on the toilet.
And thermostat's not set
to storing meat.
I did turn the
toilet paper around
so it comes over the top
like you like it.
Like the world likes it.
Don't start on this again.
(chuckles)
Hee-hee.
(chuckling)
So, we got a plan?
We got a plan.
Mm.
(sighs)
(grunts)
So I'll spend
tomorrow night at my place.
Yep.
(sighs):
Oh, thank God.
Where you going?
Think I might have
to crank up the AC.
DALE:
'Cause I said "thank God"?
MEEMAW:
No fooling you.
(quietly):
Okay, she's asleep.
I put a trash can by the bed
in case she gets sick.
Where am I supposed
to sleep?
On the floor.
Why can't she sleep
on the floor?
She doesn't even know
where she is.
I don't have time for this.
I have to find Heather
before I lose my ride home.
Fine.
But first,
we have to get
our story straight
about where I was tonight.
There's only one story,
and it's straight:
you were here.
No, I wasn't.
I was at Heather's,
and you didn't see me.
Got it?
First I have to sleep
on the floor
and now I have to lie for you?
How 'bout this?
Work with me, and I will
officially owe you one.
One what?
I don't know. One anything.
"Anything" is awfully vague.
What say we draw up
a contract or...
Sheldon, you went
to a frat party; now there's
a drunk girl in your bed.
That's the coolest college story
you'll ever get to tell.
So I can tell Mom.
No. Someday.
When?
Someday when we're old
and we can laugh about it.
I got to go.
(sighs)
ADULT SHELDON:
30 years later,
still not laughing.
(crickets chirping)
What are you
doing out here?
It's the middle
of the night.
I can't sleep
not knowing where she is.
Yeah.
(grunting)
(sighing)
So we're on the same page,
when she does show up,
I'm gonna kill her.
You're gonna have
to beat me to it.
Not saying
I love her the most,
but if anything
happened to Missy...
She is your
little girl.
Not so little anymore.
Hmm.
And I hate it.
Well, pretty soon, you're
gonna have a granddaughter.
Start all over again.
(chuckles)
(snorts)
You know,
I had an idea.
I'm gonna put a tracker on her,
like they do with dolphins.
You're making that up.
No, it's true.
Yeah, wherever she goes--
Timbuktu, doesn't matter--
we're there.
(snorts)
(both sigh)
(door opens)
MISSY:
I'm home!
(door closes)
(footsteps approaching)
Hey.
Hey to you.
How was Heather's?
Uh, fun.
Pizza, movies--
the usual.
You look tired.
I didn't sleep
too well.
Oh. Sorry.
Well, I'm gonna go to my room.
What happened to killing her?
I'll get to it.
(door closes)
Just so relieved she's okay.
(slurps, smacks lips)
Okay, I'm good. Missy!
Wait for me!
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org