BILLY: OH.
OLIVIA: HERE WE GO. OK.
WHAT IS--
WHAT IS THIS?
WELL, IT'S BLUEBERRY
AND RICOTTA TOAST.
BLUEBERRY AND RICOTTA.
WHAT--
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE EGGS AND THE
CRACKLIN' BACON AND--
I THINK IT LOOKS
GREAT, HONEY.
- IT TASTES GREAT, TOO.
- YOU SEE, DAD?
JORDAN'S INHALING HIS.
BILLY: OK.
DAD, IF YOU DON'T WANT YOURS,
I CAN TAKE IT OFF YOUR PLATE.
EXCUSE ME.
GREEDY WITH YOUR--
BILLY: LET ME--ALL RIGHT.
OLIVIA: WELL?
I STAND CORRECTED.
THIS IS DELICIOUS.
OLIVIA: I KNOW.
BILLY: ALL RIGHT.
WAY TO GO.
SO, HAVE YOU,
DECIDED WHAT YOU'RE GONNA
SAY TO YOUR TEAM TODAY?
I'M, STILL
WORKING ON IT.
OLIVIA: WAIT, WHAT'S THAT?
JORDAN:.
AFTER TODAY'S
SPRING COMBINE,
DAD'S GONNA TELL
HIS TEAM THAT HE'S
LEAVING CRENSHAW
FOR THE GAU JOB.
OLIVIA: HOW DO YOU THINK
THEY'LL TAKE IT?
BILLY: I DON'T KNOW.
COACHING CHANGE
AT THIS LEVEL, THEY HIT
A LITTLE BIT HARDER, SO...
OLIVIA:
BILLY: THE PLAYERS LOOK
AT ME AS A FATHER FIGURE.
GRACE IS GONNA BE THERE...
JORDAN:
BILLY: IF THE PLAYERS
NEED HELP AFTERWARDS.
JORDAN: AND I'LL BE THERE.
BILLY: YES.
OLIVIA: WHY ARE YOU GOING?
BECAUSE BEVERLY PLAYERS
ARE GONNA BE THERE.
I'M GONNA HELP OUT
WITH THE DRILLS,
YOU KNOW, THROWING
TO THE WIDE RECEIVERS.
BILLY: YOU THINK
ANYBODY ELSE WOULD
WANT TO HELP OUT,
LIKE--LIKE SPENCER?
I KNOW THE PLAYERS
LOOK UP TO HIM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
LAURA: BABE.
BILLY:
LAURA: IF YOU WANT
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT
WITH SPENCER,
JUST CALL HIM.
TAKE THE FIRST STEP.
OLIVIA: WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU LIKED THE BLUEBERRY
AND RICOTTA TOAST...
JORDAN:
OLIVIA: BUT I CAN'T
TAKE ALL THE CREDIT
BECAUSE IT'S LAYLA'S RECIPE.
JORDAN: WHAT?
REALLY?
NEVER MADE THIS FOR ME.
WHY WOULD LAYLA
MAKE YOU BREAKFAST?
BECAUSE WE'RE FRIENDS.
LAURA: YOU GUYS,
I MISSED THIS,
THE FOUR OF US.
BILLY: YEAH. THIS IS NICE.
WE SHOULD DO THIS
MORE OFTEN.
OLIVIA: I'M IN.
JORDAN: ME, TOO.
LAURA: YEAH?
OLIVIA: YEAH.
LAURA: SO, LIKE, WHAT?
ONCE A WEEK?
OLIVIA:...
JORDAN: WELL...
BILLY: HA HA HA!
OLIVIA: I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
LAURA, CHUCKLING:
OK, HOW 'BOUT...
ONCE A MONTH,
JUST US?
OK? THEN IT'S SETTLED.
ONCE A MONTH, BREAKFAST
WITH MY FAVOURITE TEAM.
LAURA: YEAH.
BILLY: ALL RIGHT. BRING IT IN.
LAURA: CHEERS.
BILLY: YEAH, BAKER BREAKFAST.
COOP: WAIT,
SO LIV DOESN'T WANT
TO BE FRIENDS?
NAW, SHE WANTS TO BE
MORE THAN FRIENDS.
BRO, BUT Y'ALL
TRIED THAT ALREADY
AND IT DIDN'T WORK.
"DIDN'T WORK" IS
A LITTLE OVERSIMPLIFIED,
BUT I GUESS.
NOW, LOOK, DO YOU
STILL LOVE LIV?
YES. BUT AM I STILL
IN LOVE WITH HER?
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW DO I KNOW WHAT I FEEL
WHEN I'M AROUND HER
ISN'T JUST ECHOES
FROM WHAT WE HAD?
THOSE ARE GOOD QUESTIONS.
WHAT DID ALICIA SAY?
SPENCER:
COOP: ""?
WHAT DID YOUR
CURRENT GIRLFRIEND SAY
ABOUT YOUR EX-GIRLFRIEND
WANTING YOU BACK?
SPENCER: I AIN'T TELL HER.
COOP: WHAT?
WHAT? LOOK, I'M TOO BUSY
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO SAY TO LIV,
WHO I'M KINDA
AVOIDING RIGHT NOW
'CAUSE SHE WANTS
TO MEET UP TODAY.
BRO, THERE'S WAY
TOO MUCH HISTORY
BETWEEN YOU TWO
FOR YOU TO JUST BE
BLOWING HER OFF
LIKE THAT, SO IF YOU
ARE GONNA AVOID HER,
YOU BETTER HAVE
A LEGIT REASON.
ARE YOU WEARING
A CARDIGAN?
NO, IT'S AN OFFICIAL
COASTAL CALIFORNIA
SWEATER VEST.
YOU'RE GONNA WEAR IT
TO THE COMBINE?
WELL, NOW I'M
NOT SO SURE.
IT'S FINE.
YOU LOOK COACH-Y.
ASHER: THAT'S WHAT
I WAS GOING FOR.
JAYMEE: GOOD, GOOD.
ASHER: ALL RIGHT.
WISH ME LUCK.
YOU'RE LEAVING
RIGHT NOW?
YEAH, IT'S--IT'S
A LONG DRIVE. WHY?
NOTHING. I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING,
BUT IT CAN WAIT.
IS EVERYTHING OK?
I GUESS THAT DEPENDS
ON YOUR REACTION.
TO WHAT?
I'M PREGNANT.
NOW THAT I HAVE YOUR REACTION,
ASK ME AGAIN HOW I'M DOING.
NO, I'M--
I'M--I'M SORRY.
OK, UM...
LET ME CALL
THE OTHER COACHES,
LET 'EM KNOW THAT I CAN'T
COVER THE COMBINE, OK?
WE HAVE PLENTY
OF TIME TO TALK.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT PLENTY, BUT
WE HAVE TIME.
YOU SHOULD GO
TO THE COMBINE,
WEAR YOUR LITTLE CARDIGAN.
ASHER: SWEATER VEST.
JAYMEE: HEH! YEAH. HEH!
WE CAN TALK
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
LAYLA: DAD.
HEY, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE IN TOWN.
HEY, UM, I'D LIKE TO SPEAK
WITH MY DAUGHTER ALONE, PLEASE?
MAN: YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
OK.
WELL, I CAN TELL
YOU'RE UPSET,
BUT CAN I HUG YOU
AT LEAST?
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN MONTHS. HEH!
LOOK, I'M SURE
YOU KNOW WHY I'M HERE.
UM, 'CAUSE CLAY GAVE US
OUR NAME BACK?
EVERYTHING I BUILT
AT KEATING RECORDS,
MY LIFE'S WORK, IT'S GONE.
LAYLA: WELL, THE MUSIC
CATALOGUE'S STILL THERE.
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE'S
NAME ATTACHED TO IT.
IT WAS CREATED WITH MY NAME.
RIGHT. WELL, IF THE NAME
MEANT SO MUCH TO YOU,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD'VE
LEFT IT TO SOMEONE
WHO SHARED THAT NAME.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN
YOUR LEGACY, DAD,
NOT CLAY,
AND I FIXED THAT.
HEY, I'M YOUR BLOOD
AND THE LEGACY
WILL CARRY ON.
YOU WERE SO ADAMANT
ABOUT WANTING TO BUILD
YOUR OWN THING, I DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW YOU WANTED
THE COMPANY, AND I
APOLOGISE FOR THAT.
BUT I WORKED REALLY HARD
TO BUILD KEATING RECORDS
FROM SCRATCH.
YES, YOU ARE MY LEGACY,
BUT SO IS THAT COMPANY,
AT LEAST UNTIL SOMEONE
STRIPPED MY NAME FROM IT.
SORRY.
ONE DAY
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
PREACH: A.J., WHERE YOU GOIN'?
A.J.: DETENTION.
PREACH:
DETENTION IS THAT WAY.
A.J.: I'MMA HIT UP
THE CANDY MACHINE FIRST.
PREACH: THE CANDY MACHINE
IN THE TEACHERS' LOUNGE?
A.J.: AIN'T NO TEACHERS
HERE ON SATURDAY.
PREACH: I'M HERE.
LOOK, IT'S MY JOB TO
MAKE SURE THAT YOU GET
TO DETENTION ON TIME,
BUT YOU GOT 20 SECONDS.
19, 18,
17.
AMINA: HI, DADDY.
AMINA, WHAT YOU DOIN' HERE?
I DON'T GET YOU
UNTIL NEXT WEEKEND.
MEMA DROPPED ME OFF
EARLY, SO WE CAN SPEND
THE WEEKEND TOGETHER.
NICE.
LOOK, I HAVE TO,
SUPERVISE THIS
DETENTION THING,
BUT YOU CAN HANG OUT
IN BILLY'S OFFICE.
COOP IS MEETING ME
HERE FOR LUNCH.
SHE'LL BE GLAD
TO SEE YOU.
COME HERE, BABY GIRL.
I MISS YOU.
WORKING
ANOTHER SATURDAY.
JUST DOING
SOME RESEARCH.
DID YOU HEAR
THE BIG NEWS?
OLIVIA:
CHRISTEL: YOUR ARTICLE
HAS BEEN PICKED UP
IN 8 MAJOR NEWS MARKETS.
DETROIT, ATLANTA, PHILLY.
A LOCAL MORNING SHOW
IN CHICAGO IS EVEN
RUNNING AN ON-AIR
SEGMENT ABOUT IT.
OLIVIA: WAIT. SERIOUSLY?
CHRISTEL: CONGRATULATIONS.
IT'S TOO BAD I HAD TO
TURN DOWN THE INTERVIEW,
BUT THIS IS STILL
HUGE FOR YOU, AND US.
WAIT--WHAT--
WHAT INTERVIEW?
THEY WANTED TO TALK
TO THE JOURNALIST
WHO WROTE THE ARTICLE--
JAYDEN DAVIS.
TSK.
SUCKS THAT I DON'T
GET ANY CREDIT
FOR MY OWN ARTICLE.
YOU CHOSE TO GO
THE PSEUDONYM ROUTE.
BUT EVERYONE HERE
KNOWS WHO WROTE IT.
BIG THINGS ARE COMING
TO YOU, LIV.
OLIVIA:.
YOU'RE FEELING GUILTY,
AREN'T YOU?
MY DAD JUST LOOKED
SO HEARTBROKEN.
SO WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
LAYLA: I GUESS TALK TO CLAY.
JORDAN:.
I--I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA
OF YOU HAVING TO GROVEL.
WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT GROVELING?
NOT ME.
YEAH, I DON'T GROVEL.
JORDAN: OF COURSE NOT.
LAYLA: YEAH. HEH!
JORDAN: YOU DON'T GROVEL. NO.
LAYLA: HEY.
RELAX. Y'ALL KNOW
YA AIN'T GOTTA
PRETEND IN FRONT
OF ME NO MORE.
SORRY.
FORCE OF HABIT.
JORDAN: RIGHT.
LAYLA: I SHOULD GET GOING.
YEAH. I GOTTA GET
OUTTA HERE, TOO, SO...
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
BYE, SPENCE.
SPENCER: LATER.
LAYLA: BYE.
JORDAN: ACTUALLY, YO, SPENCE.
SPENCER: YEAH?
I AM HELPING OUT AT
THE SPRING COMBINE TODAY.
YOU KNOW, JUST GIVING
SOME HIGH SCHOOL JUNIORS
A CHANCE TO SHINE.
DON'T SUPPOSE MAYBE
YOU'D WANT TO PITCH IN AND--
SPENCER: YES.
YES, DEFINITELY.
LET'S DO IT.
REALLY? OK, THAT WAS
UNEXPECTEDLY EASY.
WELL, I KINDA NEED
SOMETHING LEGIT
TO DO TODAY
TO GET OUT
OF SOMETHING ELSE,
SO THIS IS PERFECT.
MUST BE SOMETHING
YOU REALLY WANT
TO GET OUT OF BADLY
IF YOU'RE WILLING
TO SPEND TIME WITH MY DAD.
WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT SPENDING TIME
WITH YOUR DAD? NO.
NO, IT'S A BIG FIELD,
AND I'M THERE
FOR THE PLAYERS,
NOT HIM. COME ON.
OK.
BILLY: HEY, ASH.
ASHER: HEH!
BILLY: WHAT'S UP?
ASHER: HEY, COACH.
AREN'T YOU GOING
TO THE COMBINE?
YEAH. YEAH, I'M--
I'M ON MY WAY
THERE NOW.
BILLY: OK.
ASHER: I JUST WANTED
TO GET SOME ADVICE.
OH. OK.
CAN WE DISCUSS IT
AT THE COMBINE?
MY GIRLFRIEND IS
PREGNANT, COACH.
BILLY: OK.
WOW.
THAT IS THE FIRST TIME
THAT I'VE
SAID IT OUT LOUD.
IT FEELS--
BILLY: HEH HEH!
YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE IT.
ASHER: COACH, I HAVE...
A HUNDRED QUESTIONS
AND NOT ONE
SINGLE ANSWER.
BILLY: YOU'LL BE READY.
ASHER: HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE MOST
PREPARED PLAYER
I'VE EVER COACHED,
SO, WE'RE GONNA BE
JUST FINE.
OK?
NOW, WE GONNA GO
TO THIS COMBINE
OR WE'RE GONNA TALK
ABOUT YOUR KID ALL DAY?
YEAH, SORRY.
BILLY: OK.
ASHER: HEH!
I'LL, I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
BILLY: OK, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, UM,
THAT'S THE KITCHEN,
IT'S THAT DIRECTION.
SO YOU'RE IN NO CONDITION
TO DRIVE, SO WHY DON'T WE
TAKE THE CRENSHAW BUS TOGETHER?
ASHER: YEAH.
BILLY: YEAH. THERE WE GO.
ASHER: YEAH, THANKS.
BILLY: THIS WAY.
OPEN UP. THERE WE GO.
ASHER: YEAH.
YO, WHERE DID YOU
GET THESE?
WE GOT A SNACK MACHINE
IN THE TEACHERS' LOUNGE.
DAWG, I JUST
BROKE MY TOOTH.
THIS THING GOTTA BE,
LIKE, 30 YEARS OLD.
AMINA: TASTES GOOD TO ME.
COOP: WELL, THEN, SEE HERE.
YOU CAN HAVE MINE THEN.
WOMAN: AMINA.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU ABOUT
EATING THAT MUCH SUGAR?
YOU SAID IT'LL
ROT MY TEETH.
YOU NEED
SOMETHING,
MRS. MOORE?
YES. I NEED
MY GRANDDAUGHTER.
ARE YOU FORGETTING WE HAVE
FULL CUSTODY OF HER?
THIS WAS STUPID.
WHY DID YOU DROP HER OFF
EARLY IF YOU WAS GONNA
COME AT HIM LIKE THIS?
THE JUDGE IS GONNA
HEAR ABOUT THIS.
IT'S NOT HIS FAULT.
I RAN AWAY.
COOP: WAIT. WHAT?
AMINA: I'M SORRY, MEMA.
I LIED AND SAID YOU
DROPPED ME OFF EARLY
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO MOVE TO BALTIMORE.
COOP: BALTIMORE?
AIN'T NOBODY GOIN'
TO BALTIMORE.
WE ARE.
WE'RE MOVING THERE
AT THE END OF AMINA'S
SCHOOL SEMESTER.
THE HELL YOU ARE.
AMINA, LET'S GO
CHECK OUT THE GYM.
IS THIS THE PART
WHERE YOU GET ALL TOUGH
AND YOU TRY TO
INTIMIDATE ME?
NO, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
AMINA'S
OUR RESPONSIBILITY,
AND SHE'S BETTER OFF
WITHOUT YOU.
I KNOW THE REAL YOU.
I WATCHED YOU GROW UP
ON THESE STREETS,
AND THAT'S WHY
I'M TAKING HER
FAR AWAY FROM HERE,
AND NOW YOU DON'T
GET HER NEXT WEEKEND.
JORDAN:
OK, SO REWIND.
MY SISTER ASKED YOU
TO GET BACK TOGETHER?
SPENCER: YEP.
JORDAN: AND YOU
DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING?
SHE AIN'T GIVE ME
A CHANCE.
BUT SHE WANTED
TO TALK TODAY
AND INSTEAD,
YOU'RE DOING THE COMBINE?
SPENCER: BRO,
YOU ASKED ME
FOR MY HELP.
NAH. YOU ARE JUST
AVOIDING HER.
THAT IS NOT COOL.
SPENCER: WHOSE SIDE
ARE YOU ON, DAWG?
JORDAN: MY SISTER'S.
OK, LOOK, COOL.
YOU WANT ME
TO LEAVE, I'LL LEAVE.
JORDAN: NO, NO, NO, NO.
COME ON. WE'RE ALREADY
HERE, ALL RIGHT?
BESIDES, YOU PROBABLY
ALREADY BLEW IT
WITH LIV, BUT MY DAD WAS
GLAD YOU AGREED TO COME.
SPENCER: WHY'D YOU TELL HIM?
JORDAN: 'CAUSE IT WAS HIS IDEA.
HE ASKED YOU
TO BRING ME HERE?
I MEAN, HE MENTIONED IT.
IT WASN'T LIKE IT WAS
SOME DEVIOUS PLAN.
BRO, NOW HE'S GONNA
THINK I'M ACCEPTING
SOME OLIVE BRANCH THAT
I AIN'T READY FOR YET.
YOU GOTTA RELAX,
DUDE, OK?
YOU ARE THE ONE WHO IS
MAKING EVERYTHING
MORE COMPLICATED HERE,
ALL RIGHT, WITH OLIVIA
AND MY DAD.
I'MMA GO CHECK OUT
THESE WIDE RECEIVERS.
I...
CLAY, CHUCKLING:
YEAH, THIS LOOKS GOOD.
I LIKE THAT.
YOU DIDN'T
WASTE ANY TIME.
REBRANDING IS OUR
MAIN FOCUS RIGHT NOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
LAYLA: CLAY TAYLOR
ENTERTAINMENT?
YOU REALLY GOING
WITH THE INITIALS?
CLAY: IT'S OUR NEW LOGO. WHY?
LAYLA: CTE?
CLAY:
YOU KNOW THAT'S
A SPORTS INJURY-RELATED
BRAIN CONDITION, RIGHT?
CAN I HELP YOU
WITH SOMETHING?
YES, ACTUALLY.
GOOD NEWS.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO USE THE CTE LOGO.
IT'S CLAY TAYLOR
ENTERTAINMENT.
LAYLA: NO, IT'S KEATING RECORDS.
CLAY: WHAT?
YOU CAN HAVE
THE NAME BACK.
I WAS WRONG.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU WERE WRONG,
OR DID DADDY SAY
YOU WERE WRONG?
DOES IT MATTER?
YOU CAN HAVE
THE NAME BACK.
CONGRATULATIONS. YOU WIN.
CLAY: I ALREADY WON.
I GOT THE ARTISTS,
THE CATALOGUE,
AND THE EMPIRE.
NOW IT'S ALL UNDER MY NAME.
LAYLA: CTE.
IT'S CLAY TAYLOR
ENTERTAI--
LOOK, THE BALL IS
ALREADY ROLLING
ON THIS REBRANDING.
IT'S TOO LATE,
SO YOU CAN KEEP
THE KEATING NAME.
NOW GO WORK
ON THEM DADDY ISSUES
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
I HAVE AN EMPIRE
TO RUN HERE.
D, LET ME HOLLER
AT YOU RIGHT QUICK.
THIS LOOKS GOOD, MAN.
MAYBE WE CAN GET
ANOTHER SIGN RIGHT HERE...
CRENSHAW GOT SOME
CRAZY TALENT
COMING BACK
NEXT YEAR, COACH.
BILLY: HEH HEH! YES, SIR.
SHAME I AIN'T GONNA BE
OUT THERE WITH 'EM.
OH, COME ON, NOW.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE
GONNA BE BALLIN'
OUT THERE AT COASTAL.
JABARI:
BILLY: ONLY BIGGER AND
BETTER THINGS FOR YOU, SON.
JABARI: WHAT ABOUT YOU?
BILLY:
BIGGER AND BETTER THINGS
IN YOUR FUTURE, TOO?
THERE'S A LOT OF SMOKE
ABOUT YOU LEAVING...
BILLY: YEAH.
SO GUYS ARE STARTING
TO ASK QUESTIONS.
BILLY: I'MMA TELL
THE TEAM TODAY.
JABARI: WELL, WHATEVER
YOU DECIDE, COACH,
I GOT YOUR BACK
'CAUSE, I MEAN,
WITHOUT YOU...
IF I DIDN'T
COME PLAY FOR YOU,
THERE WOULD BE NO BIGGER
AND BETTER IN MY FUTURE.
COME ON, MAN.
I'LL NEVER FORGET
EVERYTHING YOU DID
FOR ME, COACH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
THANK YOU, SON.
GET OUTTA HERE.
HEY, COACH.
OH, IT'S MY HUSBAND'S
ACE RECRUITER.
HEH HEH.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I MEAN, YOU WERE
MY SECRET WEAPON
AND NOW YOU'RE HIS.
ASHER, CHUCKLING: YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU JUST HAD
ANOTHER GREAT SEASON
AT BEVERLY WITHOUT ME.
AH, WELL, WHEN YOU
WERE BY MY SIDE, IT WAS
DEFINITELY A LOT EASIER.
ASHER: I DO WANT
TO KNOW YOUR SECRET.
MONTES: TO COACHING?
ASHER: YES.
MONTES: HYDRATION.
ASHER: SUCH A MONTES ANSWER.
BILLY: OH, WHAT'S
HAPPENING HERE?
ASHER: COACH.
BILLY: BEVERLY REUNION
IN THE HOUSE.
MONTES: HEY, COACH.
BILLY: GOOD TO SEE YOU.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
SO, HOW'S...
HOW'S MY OLD OFFICE?
JUST KEEP ADDING
BANNERS TO IT.
I WAS JUST ASKING
MONTES HER SECRET
TO COACHING.
WHAT'S YOURS?
I'M NOT GIVING YOU
MY SECRETS.
WE'RE RIVALS
NEXT YEAR, BRUH.
YEAH.
ASHER: YEAH. I,
I KEEP FORGETTING.
BILLY: YUP.
LOOK, UM...
I WANT YOU BOTH
TO KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU'VE MEANT TO ME.
YOU BOTH HELPED ME
BECOME THE PERSON
THAT I AM TODAY.
NOW I'M--I'M
GONNA WALK AWAY
'CAUSE I KNOW MONTES
HATES THESE MOMENTS.
BILLY: HA HA!
I DO, BUT,
THANK YOU, COACH ADAMS.
ASHER: WELCOME.
BILLY: THANK YOU, SIR.
IT'S BEEN A PLEASURE.
SO THE RUMOURS
ARE TRUE.
YOU AND ADAMS ARE GONNA
BE RIVALS NEXT YEAR?
YEAH, YEAH.
I, HAVEN'T...
HAVEN'T TOLD
MY TEAM YET.
DO YOU EVER THINK
ABOUT WHAT YOUR
NEXT STEP IS GONNA BE?
BEVERLY IS
MY NEXT STEP.
I MEAN, LOOK AT WHAT
WE GET TO DO.
I LOVE THIS.
AND THESE KIDS NEED US,
THEY LOOK UP TO US,
AND THEY STILL LOVE
FOOTBALL.
YOU KNOW,
SOME PEOPLE ASSUME
THAT I HAVEN'T APPLIED
TO A D-1 JOB BECAUSE
I'M A WOMAN, BUT,
REALLY,
IT'S BECAUSE...I'M
RIGHT WHERE I BELONG.
DOESN'T GET
ANY BETTER THAN THIS,
AND I'M SURE THAT YOU
HAVE YOUR REASONS
FOR MOVING ON,
BUT...I'D BE CRAZY
TO LEAVE.
SPENCER, VOICE-OVER:
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
A GREAT COACH AT GAU,
BUT YOU'RE A GREAT MAN
IN CRENSHAW.
YOU'D BE INSANE
TO WALK AWAY FROM THAT.
NICE GRAB, NICE GRAB,
NICE GRAB.
YOU UP, CRAWFORD.
LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
SPENCE, SQUAD ABOUT
TO BE LEGIT NEXT YEAR.
'BOUT TO GET
COACH BAKER HIS SECOND
STATE CHAMPIONSHIP.
YOU UP, MAN. LET'S GO.
GO GET IT. GO GET IT.
SPENCER: EDDY.
COME HERE, MAN.
EDDY: HA HA HA!
YO, SPENCE.
SPENCER: WHAT'S FUNNY?
YOU OUT THERE DROPPING
EASY PASSES AND LAUGHING?
WHAT'S FUNNY ABOUT
HAVING STONE HANDS, BRUH?
YO, YOU AIN'T GOTTA DO ME
LIKE THAT, BIG DAWG.
I DROPPED A PASS.
I'LL CATCH THE NEXT ONE.
NO BIG DEAL.
NO, NO, IT IS A BIG DEAL.
IT AIN'T ABOUT
THE DROPPED BALL, MAN.
IT'S ABOUT YOU SHOWING
ALL THOSE COLLEGE COACHES
THAT YOU DON'T CARE.
LOOK, WE ALL KNOW
YOU GOT BIG TALENT.
DO NOT GIVE THESE COACHES
A REASON TO PASS ON YOU,
MAN. COME ON.
EDDY: YES, SIR.
SPENCER: LET'S GO.
EVERYBODY, IT'S
SPENCER JAMES.
HA HA HA HA!
MAN, I JUST HAD
A VERY SCARY FLASHBACK
TO YOU GETTING ON ME
AT PRACTICE.
SPENCER: HEY,
IT WORKED, DIDN'T IT?
OH...
SO YOU TAKING
FULL CREDIT FOR MY
SCHOLLIE AT COASTAL?
NAH.
NO, YOU EARNED THAT.
YOU DEFINITELY
HELPED, THOUGH.
SPENCER:
JABARI: THAT'S FOR SURE.
MAN, YOU LUCKY.
YOU GET TO BE REUNITED
WITH COACH BAKER
AT GAU NEXT YEAR.
YEAH, BUT AT WHAT COST?
LOOK, IF YOU ASK ME,
COASTAL'S THE LUCKY ONE.
THEY GOT THEMSELVES A STAR.
BUT YOU KNOW WE GONNA
HAVE TO PLAY EACH OTHER
NEXT YEAR, RIGHT?
YEAH, OCTOBER 7.
YOU ALREADY KNOW
THE DATE?
JABARI: OH, IT'S BEEN CIRCLED.
SPENCER: HA HA HA!
JABARI:
YOU BETTER BE READY, MAN.
SPENCER: BOY, I STAY READY.
JABARI: I HOPE SO.
HEY, GOOD TO SEE YOU, BRO.
SPENCER: PROUD OF YOU, MAN.
HEY, THANK YOU.
LET'S GO, 14.
SPENCER: AH!
THERE YOU GO, THERE YOU GO.
JABARI: GOOD STUFF.
THAT'S WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT, EDDY.
SADIE MOORE: TAMIA.
COOP: HEY, MS. MOORE.
WHERE'S YOUR MUM?
COOP: SHE AIN'T COMIN'.
SADIE: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH HER. SHE TOLD ME TO
MEET HER HERE FOR COFFEE.
I ASKED HER TO DO THAT
BECAUSE I KNEW YOU
WOULDN'T MEET WITH ME.
TAMIA, I KNOW WHAT YOU
GONNA SAY, AND IT
AIN'T GONNA WORK.
CAN WE PLEASE JUST
HAVE THE COFFEE?
ALL RIGHT, I ORDERED
YOURS ALREADY.
SADIE:.
AND THEN YOU CAN CALL
AND YELL AT MY MUM LATER.
OH, I'LL CALL HER.
SHE'LL PROBABLY BE
WAITING ON IT.
SO...
SHE TOLD ME YOU WERE
WORKING IN A LAW FIRM?
YEAH. I AM.
YOU HAVE REALLY TURNED
YOUR LIFE AROUND?
I HAVE,
AND SO HAS PREACH.
WE'RE MOVING
TO BALTIMORE, TAMIA.
OK, BUT DON'T MOVE
BECAUSE YOU THINK
YOU'RE PROTECTING AMINA
FROM HER DAD, ALL RIGHT?
NOT UNTIL YOU GET
TO KNOW THE REAL PREACH.
OH, I KNOW HIM.
I WATCHED HIM GROW UP.
AND YOU WATCHED ME
GROW UP, AND YOU JUST SAID
YOURSELF I WAS ABLE
TO TURN MY LIFE AROUND.
WHY ARE YOU SO SURE
HE CAN'T TURN HIS AROUND?
YOU GONNA TALK TO HIM?
I ALREADY DID
THE OTHER DAY.
AIN'T NOTHING
LEFT TO SAY.
IF THAT WAS TRUE,
YOU WOULDN'T BE HERE.
I'M JUST HELPING OUT
AND AVOIDING LIV.
GRACE: WHY?
SPENCER: SHE WANTS
TO GET BACK TOGETHER.
GRACE: IS THAT A BAD THING?
I DON'T KNOW YET.
I MEAN,
WHAT'S REALLY CHANGED
SINCE WE BROKE UP, MA?
YOU HAVE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT
AS HAPPY, BABY.
I'M JUST
ACKNOWLEDGING A FACT.
GRACE: OK.
I'MMA LET YOU
SIT WITH THAT,
BUT AS FOR BILLY--
SPENCER: WHY'D YOU
FORGIVE HIM SO EASY?
FIRST OFF, BILLY DIDN'T
NEED MY FORGIVENESS.
I MEAN, I CONFRONTED HIM,
I SPOKE MY PIECE,
WE'RE MOVING ON.
YOU AIN'T GONNA BE
DIVIDED FOREVER.
SPENCER: LOOK, I TOLD YOU,
I ALREADY SAID MY PIECE, MA.
GRACE: DID YOU?
'CAUSE IT SEEMS LIKE YOU
MIGHT HAVE A LITTLE MORE
THAT NEEDS TO BE SAID.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
UM, IT'S GOOD.
IT'S GREAT.
YEAH. THAT'S WHAT I
WANTED TO HEAR. HEH HEH!
UM, NOW CAN I SAY
SOMETHING YOU MIGHT
NOT WANT TO HEAR?
HEY, UM, I JUST FEEL
LIKE IT'S MISSING
SOMETHING.
SOME OF THE LEVELS
ARE A BIT ROUGH.
YOU KNOW, I'D--I'D JUST
GET RID OF THE FLUFF,
AND IT FEELS A BIT
CROWDED. I DON'T THINK
YOU NEED TO FILL
ALL THAT SPACE 'CAUSE
HER VOICE IS SO STRONG.
ANYTHING ELSE?
UM, WELL, THE REVERB
AT THE BEGINNING
HAS GOTTA GO.
I MEAN, YOU COULD--YOU
COULD ADD SOME COMPRESSION
IN A FEW SPOTS
OR TRY IT AND SEE
WHERE IT GETS YOU.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
WE CAN EVEN ADD SOME
NOW IF YOU'VE GOT TIME.
YES, PLEASE, YEAH.
LAYLA: OK. DAD.
JP: HEY. THIS A BAD TIME?
HI. UM, YOU KNOW
SHAWN STOCKMAN.
JP: OH, HEY, IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
BUT WE GO WAY BACK. COME ON.
SHAWN: GOOD TO SEE YOU.
JP, CHUCKLING:
HEY, HEY.
YOU KNOW HOW MANY TIMES
THIS GUY TURNED ME DOWN?
IT WAS NEVER
REALLY THE RIGHT TIME.
JP: YEAH, RIGHT.
SHAWN: HA HA HA!
JP: HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
SHAWN: ACTUALLY, I'M HERE
TO TEST YOUR DAUGHTER OUT, MAN.
SHE'S MAKING A HELL OF A NAME
FOR HERSELF,
AND NOW I BELIEVE
THE HYPE.
LAYLA: SO YOU KNEW
WHAT WAS MISSING.
SHAWN: HEH!
I DID, UM, AND I
NEEDED YOU TO HEAR
THE SAME THING,
THAT IS, IF WE'RE GONNA
PRODUCE THIS SONG TOGETHER.
WAIT. ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU--YOU WANT TO
PRODUCE WITH ME?
SHAWN: LISTEN.
I'VE SENT THIS SONG
TO ABOUT
20 PRODUCERS OR MORE,
AND YOU KNOW HOW MANY
CRITICISED IT?
JUST YOU.
I DON'T NEED
SOMEONE TO TELL ME
THAT THE SONG
IS GOOD.
I NEED SOMEONE TO HELP ME
MAKE THE SONG GREAT.
WELL, I'M IN,
AND I'M HONOURED. HEH!
UM, DAD, CAN WE
TALK LATER? I'LL JUST--
JP: HEY, DO YOUR THING.
HEY, SHAWN,
IT'S GOOD SEEING YOU, BRO.
SHAWN: GOOD TO SEE YOU, BRO.
JP: ALL RIGHT. COOL.
SHAWN: ALL RIGHT. TAKE CARE.
UM, OK. I JUST WANT
TO LISTEN TO IT
ONE MORE TIME AND
THEN TRY SOME THINGS.
SHAWN: YEAH. LET'S DO IT.
LAYLA: OK, GREAT.
OH.
SPENCER: I GOT TO
GET GOING. YOU GOOD?
YEAH, YEAH.
I'LL FIND A RIDE.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
COACH, YOU GOT A SECOND?
BILLY: YEAH.
I GOT TO GET GOING.
OK, WELL,
THANKS FOR COMING OUT,
HELPING WITH THE,
WIDE RECEIVERS.
APPRECIATE THAT.
LOT OF TALENT
ON THIS FIELD.
YEAH.
IT'S GONNA BE
A BRIGHT FUTURE.
LOOK, I STAND
BY WHAT I SAID.
YOU'D BE CRAZY TO LEAVE
SOUTH CRENSHAW HIGH,
BUT IF YOU'RE
GONNA DO IT,
JUST RIP THE
BAND-AID OFF, MAN.
WORKING WITH
YOUR PLAYERS TODAY,
THEY SO EXCITED
ABOUT NEXT SEASON,
EVEN TALKING 'BOUT
GETTING THEIR COACH
ANOTHER CHAMPIONSHIP.
THEY GONNA TAKE IT HARD,
KNOWING YOU'RE LEAVING,
AND THE LONGER YOU WAIT,
THE HARDER IT'S GONNA BE.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
I, WAS GONNA
TELL 'EM TODAY,
BUT I THINK I'M GONNA
NEED A LITTLE BIT
MORE TIME
'CAUSE MY HEAD'S BEEN
SWIRLING ALL AROUND.
IT'S NEVER GONNA BE
THE RIGHT TIME.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE BLINDSIDED.
DO NOT DO THAT
TO THESE KIDS.
THEY GOT ENOUGH OBSTACLES
THEY GOTTA FACE.
THEY DON'T NEED THE MAN
THEY LOOK UP TO MOST
STRINGING THEM ALONG,
ACTING LIKE HE ALWAYS
GONNA BE THERE FOR 'EM.
YEAH.
SO WHAT ABOUT
YOU AND ME?
I NEED TIME.
I JUST NEED MORE TIME.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.
COME ON, MAN!
A.J.: BITCH, I WILL
RIP YOUR HAIR OUT.
GIRL: GIRL, GET
YOUR HANDS UP OFF ME!
PREACH: WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
WHAT THE HELL? I KNOW
Y'ALL NOT FIGHTING
IN MY HALLWAY!
WHAT IS THIS ABOUT?!
A.J.: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I WAS JUST TAKING
OUT THE TRASH.
LOOK, Y'ALL CAN'T BE
FIGHTING IN HERE.
A.J.: THEN WE CAN GO OUTSIDE.
PREACH: LOOK, IF I REPORT
THIS, YOU'RE BOTH
GETTING EXPELLED.
A.J.: HEH! WE KNOW YOU
AIN'T REPORTING NOTHING.
PREACH: WHY WON'T I?
MY BROTHER SAYS NOBODY
MESSES WITH PREACH.
YOU WAS IN PRISON,
RIGHT?
PREACH: SEE, WHAT YOUR BROTHER
SHOULD BE SAYING IS I'M
AN EXAMPLE OF HOW SOMEONE CAN
TURN THEIR LIFE AROUND.
IT AIN'T ABOUT
THAT LIFE NO MORE.
I GOT
A DAUGHTER NOW,
A FEW YEARS YOUNGER
THAN BOTH OF YOU,
AND I'LL TELL HER
LIKE I'MMA TELL YOU.
NO ONE CAN MAKE
YOUR LIFE EASIER,
BUT YOU CAN MAKE IT
HARDER.
A.J.: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
PREACH: IT MEANS NOBODY'S GONNA
OPEN THE DOORS FOR YOU,
BUT IF Y'ALL KEEP
ACTING LIKE THIS,
THERE'S PEOPLE OUT THERE
THAT CAN'T WAIT TO CLOSE
THE DOOR IN YOUR FACE.
LOOK, STOP ACTING LIKE FOOLS
AND STOP FIGHTING,
AND YOU'RE GOOD.
NOW GET YOUR BAGS.
ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL.
GATHER ROUND. BRING IT IN.
BRING IT IN.
ALL RIGHT.
HA HA HA!
LOOK AT Y'ALL.
I GOTTA SAY, I'M PROUD
OF Y'ALL EFFORT OUT THERE.
Y'ALL DID Y'ALL THINGS IN FRONT
OF THOSE COLLEGE COACHES,
AND BELIEVE ME,
THIS WILL GO A LONG WAY
TO BIGGER AND BETTER THINGS
WHEN IT COMES TO YOUR FUTURE.
I HAVE NO DOUBT
THAT EACH AND EVERY ONE
OF YOUR SENIOR SEASONS,
Y'ALL GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
GIVE YOURSELVES A HAND,
ALL RIGHT?
PLAYERS: YEAH.
BILLY: ALL RIGHT.
THAT BEING SAID,
I KNOW THAT THERE HAVE
BEEN A LOT OF RUMOURS
FLOATING AROUND
'BOUT MY FUTURE,
AND I JUST WANTED Y'ALL
TO HEAR IT FROM ME.
THOSE RUMOURS ARE TRUE.
I HAVE BEEN OFFERED
THE HEAD-COACHING POSITION
AT GAU,
AND, UM--
AND I'VE ACCEPTED IT...
PLAYERS:...
BILLY: BUT HOLD UP, HOLD UP.
I AIN'T DONE, I AIN'T DONE.
I HAVE ALSO BEEN DOING
SOME SOUL-SEARCHING
THE PAST COUPLE DAYS,
AND...
AFTER SEEING WHAT Y'ALL
WERE DOING OUT THERE
ON THAT FIELD TODAY,
WORKING HARD AS HELL
TO MAKE CRENSHAW
A BETTER TEAM NEXT YEAR,
I REALIZED I MADE
A MISTAKE. YEAH.
SOMEBODY REALLY CLOSE TO ME
JUST TOLD ME THAT I WOULD BE
CRAZY TO LEAVE CRENSHAW,
TO LEAVE THE MAN
THAT CRENSHAW MADE ME,
AND HE WAS RIGHT.
JABARI: SO YOU STAYING, COACH?
BILLY: I'M SAYING I'M RIGHT
HERE WHERE I BELONG.
PLAYERS: YEAH!
WHOO!
HEY, THINK FAST, OLD MAN.
BILLY: HA!
JORDAN: OOH!
BILLY: "OLD MAN"? HA HA HA!
JORDAN: YEP.
OOH, THAT'S
A LITTLE WOBBLY.
BILLY: HA HA HA!
JORDAN: AND YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO TAUGHT ME HOW
TO THROW A SPIRAL.
OH, I'VE NEVER HAD
YOUR ARM, THOUGH.
YEAH, BUT YOU HAD
SOME WHEELS.
I DID HAVE WHEELS.
YOU KNOW, THAT SPEECH
WAS A SURPRISE.
OH, NOW, YEAH, I'M
SORRY ABOUT THAT, SON.
NAH, COME ON.
YOU DON'T GOT TO APOLOGISE.
I WILL BE FINE.
WHEN YOU LEFT BEVERLY,
I HAD COACH MONTES,
AND THERE'S GONNA BE
PLENTY OF COACHES
IN MY FUTURE,
BUT ONLY ONE DAD.
HA HA HA!
YEAH.
I ACTUALLY CHANGED
MY MIND
IN THE MOMENT...'CAUSE I
HAD BEEN STRUGGLING
WITH WHAT I WAS GONNA SAY
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS, AND
THEN I SAW WHAT
THE BOYS WERE DOING OUT
THERE, AND I REALISED--
- YOU'RE RIGHT WHERE YOU BELONG.
- YEAH.
I LOVED HEARING THAT.
IT MADE ME HAPPY.
LOOK...IF YOU WANT
TO RE-ENTER
THE TRANSFER PORTAL,
I CAN MAKE A COUPLE
OF CALLS
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE I PUT
YOU IN A BAD POSITION.
NAH, NAH, NAH.
I THINK I'M RIGHT
WHERE I BELONG, TOO.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU DO SEEM HAPPIER
THAN I'VE SEEN YOU NOW
IN A LONG TIME.
YEAH, LOVE CAN
DO THAT TO YOU.
JORDAN: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
BILLY: COME ON, MAN.
YOU HAVE THE WORST
POKER FACE EVER,
ESPECIALLY WITH ME.
OH, THE BUS IS ABOUT
TO LEAVE. LOOK,
YOU TELL LAYLA...
SHE OFFICIALLY
HAS MY APPROVAL.
NOW, HOW DID YOU--
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
I'M YOUR FATHER.
I LOVE YOU, DAD.
BRING IT IN.
LOVE YOU, TOO.
- HERE YOU GO.
- SEE YOU IN A BIT.
YEP. HIGH
AND TIGHT, NOW.
HA HA!
HA HA HA!
HEY, YOU
STILL BUSY?
HI. UM, I AM
ALWAYS BUSY.
HOW DID YOU LINK UP
WITH SHAWN ANYWAY?
LAYLA: A FRIEND OF A FRIEND.
JP: AND DID YOU TELL HIM
YOU USED TO HAVE
A BOYZ II MEN POSTER
GROWING UP?
LAYLA: UM...
JP: NO.
JP: LOOK, UM,
LAYLA--
LAYLA: CLAY SAID NO, DAD.
I TOLD HIM HE COULD HAVE
THE KEATING NAME BACK,
AND HE SAID NO,
SO I KNOW YOU WANTED ME
TO FIX IT, BUT I CAN'T.
SORRY.
JP: I'M GLAD.
LAYLA: YOU'RE GLAD I'M SORRY?
NO, I'M GLAD YOU
COULDN'T FIX IT.
HE DIDN'T DESERVE
OUR NAME ANYWAY.
LAYLA: AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
JP: YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES
I FORGET YOU'RE
ONLY 19 YEARS OLD.
YOU KNOW WHAT I WAS
DOING WHEN I WAS 19?
NOT THIS,
NOT BUILDING
AN EMPIRE.
I WAS WASHING DISHES
AT A 24-HOUR DINER.
I MEAN, I WANTED
ALL THIS, BUT...
IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
YOU NEVER TOLD ME
ABOUT THAT.
CHECK IT OUT. HEH!
- YOU SEE THIS OLD NAPKIN?
- YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WHEN I WAS WORKING
AT THAT DINER,
I DREW...
THIS LOGO
FOR KEATING RECORDS.
DAD, THAT--HEH!--
SHOULD BE IN A MUSEUM.
YEAH, I MEAN,
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO CREATE SOMETHING
THAT WOULD LIVE,
YOU KNOW, AFTER I WAS
GONE AND IF I WAS LUCKY,
I WOULD HAVE A CHILD
TO BE MY BLOOD LEGACY,
AND THEN MY MUSIC
WOULD BE MY SOUL LEGACY.
WELL, I RUINED
THAT PART.
NO, YOU ARE THAT PART.
YOU ARE MY LEGACY
IN EVERY FORM, LAYLA.
I'M JUST SORRY
IT TOOK ME SO LONG
TO REALISE THAT,
AND I'M GLAD
YOU GOT OUR NAME BACK
BECAUSE NOW, MY BLOOD
AND MY SOUL ARE
BACK UNDER ONE ROOF,
AND YOU ARE GONNA TAKE
OUR KEATING LEGACY
TO LEVELS I COULD
ONLY DREAM OF
WHEN I WAS WASHING
DISHES IN THIS DINER.
THANKS, DAD.
HEY.
GRACE: HEY.
BILLY: THANKS FOR COMING TODAY.
TURNS OUT I WASN'T
NEEDED HERE.
YEAH, I, MADE
A QUICK U-TURN.
GRACE, CHUCKLING: CAN I ASK WHY?
BILLY: SPENCER.
HE WAS RIGHT,
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
HE USUALLY IS.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
TELL HIM THAT.
YEAH. I'LL SEE YOU
BACK AT SCHOOL.
YEAH.
OK.
ALL RIGHT, SPENCE.
TIME TO SPEAK YOUR PIECE
ONE MORE TIME.
SPENCER, ON VOICEMAIL:
OH, THIS IS SPENCER.
LEAVE A MESSAGE.
HEY, SPENCE, UM,
I KNOW YOU SAID THAT YOU...
YOU NEEDED SOME TIME,
AND I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
THAT, BUT I JUST--
I JUST WANT YOU
TO KNOW THAT...
YOU WERE RIGHT.
YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
HI, DADDY.
AMINA, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU KEEP RUNNING AWAY,
YOUR GRANDMA'S GONNA MOVE
YOU OUT OF THE COUNTRY.
SADIE: NO...
I WON'T.
CAN I SPEAK TO YOUR DAD
ALONE, PLEASE?
IT'S POSSIBLE
I MISJUDGED YOU.
I TOLD YOU AMINA WOULD BE
BETTER OFF WITHOUT YOU,
BUT I CAN SEE HOW MUCH
SHE NEEDS YOU.
THANK YOU.
BUT SHE NEEDS US, TOO.
MY HUSBAND AND I,
WE LOVE HER MORE
THAN ANYTHING
IN THIS WORLD.
SHE'S ALL
WE HAVE LEFT.
I KNOW.
SO, I...
I'M WILLING TO PROPOSE
A SHARED-CUSTODY
AGREEMENT.
REALLY? NO BALTIMORE?
NO BALTIMORE.
WE WERE THINKING
2 OR 3 WEEKENDS A MONTH?
I'LL TAKE IT.
I'LL TAKE ANY TIME I
CAN HAVE WITH MY BABY.
I WISH IT WAS MORE
THAN THAT, BUT I ACCEPT.
NO, YOU MISUNDERSTOOD.
WE WERE THINKING
THAT WE WOULD HAVE AMINA
2 OR 3 WEEKENDS
A MONTH AND
SHE'D LIVE WITH YOU,
FULL-TIME.
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T
ALWAYS HAVE TO BE
WORKING, MAN.
YOU CAN TAKE A BREAK.
OH, IT'S--IT'S NOT WORK.
I'VE ALREADY FINISHED THAT.
I'M WRITING OUT ALL
THE QUESTIONS I HAVE
ABOUT BEING A DAD.
FOR REAL?
I MEAN...
WELL,
I GUARANTEE YOU,
EVEN I WON'T
BE ABLE TO ANSWER
ALL THESE QUESTIONS
WE HAVE HERE.
"WHAT AGE DO THEY
START WALKING?"
WELL?
UM, HONESTLY--HEH!--
I DON'T REMEM--ONE?
I FORGET. 1 1/2, MAN?
NEXT QUESTION.
"WHAT IS SWAD--"
I CAN'T READ
YOUR HANDWRITING.
WHAT DOES THIS SAY?
"SWADLING"?
"WHAT IS SWADLING?"
ASHER: "WHAT IS SWADDLING?"
"WHAT IS SWADDLING?"
WHAT THE HELL IS--
WHAT IS SWADDLING?
ASHER: I HAVE NO IDEA.
SSS. ALL RIGHT.
FORGET THIS LIST.
UM, YOU'RE GONNA
BE FINE, MAN. JUST--
YOU'RE GONNA FIGURE
IT OUT ALL ON YOUR
OWN, JUST LIKE I DID.
YOU'LL BE COOL,
TOTALLY COOL.
ASHER: WAS IT SCARY?
BILLY: OH, HEH HEH!
IT WAS TERRIFYING,
BUT IT'S WORTH IT.
IT'S WORTH IT. UM...
I REMEMBER WHEN,
LIV WAS A BABY,
SHE USED TO DO
THIS ONE THING
WHERE SHE'D REACH--
REACH OUT HER ARM
AND JUST GRAB A HOLD
OF MY EAR.
AH, I USED TO LET HER
DO THAT FOR HOURS.
SHE WAS PERFECT.
YOU ASKED ME,
WHAT THE SECRET
TO COACHING WAS,
AND, UM...
IT'S SIMPLE, MAN.
I JUST TRY TO ACT
LIKE A FATHER TO THE
PLAYERS, YOU KNOW.
LIKE, YOU ARE
ALL MY KIDS,
AND TO BE HONEST...
YOU WERE ONE
OF MY FAVOURITES.
YEAH, JUST TRY TO BE
SOMEONE THAT THEY'D
LOOK UP TO, YOU KNOW?
ALL YOU CAN DO IS
TRY TO POINT THEM
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION
AND HOPE THEY STAY
ON THAT PATH.
YOU PUT ME ON
THE RIGHT PATH.
I TRIED MY BEST
WITH ALL OF Y'ALL.
YOU GOT A BIG HEART.
YOU'RE A GREAT COACH,
AND YOU'LL BE
AN EVEN BETTER FATHER.
HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE
TO FIGURE IT OUT?
AH, SEE, THAT'S
THE BEST PART
OF ALL THIS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW LONG IT'S GONNA
TAKE TO FIGURE IT OUT
BECAUSE THE ONE THING
YOU HAVE IS TIME.
GRACE: OH, MY LORD.
JORDAN: I DON'T SEE MY DAD.
GRACE: MAYBE YOU SHOULD
STAY IN THE CAR.
JORDAN: NO.
THERE'S ASHER.
JORDAN: ASH,
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED?
ASHER: I DON'T KNOW.
GRACE: YOU'RE BLEEDING.
ARE YOU OK?
ASHER: YEAH, I THINK SO.
BILLY: OK, ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
OK, TAKE IT
NICE AND EASY.
GRACE: JORDAN!
DAD!
OH, YOU ALL RIGHT?
OLIVIA: HEY, I'M HEADED OUT.
CHRISTEL: OK.
OH, BEFORE YOU GO,
I HAVE SOME MORE NEWS.
LET ME GUESS.
THEY WANT JAYDEN DAVIS
TO DO THE "TODAY" SHOW?
CHRISTEL: CLOSE.
THE ARTICLE'S
BEEN NOMINATED
FOR A BARDO
JOURNALISM AWARD.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD!
WAIT. BUT IF I WIN,
I CAN'T ACCEPT THE AWARD.
WOMAN: CHRISTEL, WE'RE GETTING
SOME CONFLICTING REPORTS
ON A BUS CRASH.
SOUNDS LIKE IT WAS
A FOOTBALL TEAM?
CHRISTEL: OK.
WAIT. WHAT?
W-WHERE WAS THE CRASH?
LAURA: HELLO?
OLIVIA: HEY, WHERE ARE YOU?
LAURA: I'M AT YOUR PLACE,
ACTUALLY. I JUST CAME BY
TO GIVE COOP SOME GOOD NEWS.
OLIVIA: TURN ON THE TV,
CHANNEL 6.
- WHY?
- JUST DO IT.
MAN, ON TV: AS OF NOW,
WE STILL HAVE VERY FEW
DETAILS, BUT WE'RE HEARING
A BUS CARRYING A HIGH-SCHOOL
FOOTBALL TEAM CRASHED.
FIRST RESPONDERS ARE
STILL HAVING A HARD TIME
GETTING TO THE SCENE.
LAURA: OH, MY GOD.
OLIVIA: MUM, I THINK
THAT'S DAD'S BUS.
JUST STAY THERE. I'M ON MY WAY.
LAURA: OK.
BILLY: ALL RIGHT.
MAKE SURE HE STAYS OFF
THAT LEG, ALL RIGHT?
OK.
I THINK I GOT
EVERYBODY OUT.
GRACE: YEAH. ARE YOU OK?
BILLY: YEAH, YEAH.
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
JORDAN: OK. DAD--
BILLY: ASHER,
ASHER, HOW'S HIS ARM?
GRACE: WE WRAPPED IT.
HE'S DOING OK.
BILLY: OK.
- DAD, DAD, MAYBE--
- YEAH?
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD
SIT DOWN, REST.
NO, NO, NO.
I'M GOOD. I'M GOOD.
IT HAPPENED SO FAST.
IT ALL HAPPENED SO FAST...
JORDAN: YEAH, THEY--
THEY SAID A TIRE BLEW OUT.
WELL, I THINK I GOT
EVERYBODY OUT, THOUGH.
GOT EVERYBODY OUT.
JORDAN: DAD. DAD?
BILLY: YEAH?
GRACE: BILLY,
IT'S OK.
BILLY: YEAH, YEAH.
GRACE: EVERYTHING'S OK.
BILLY: OK.
I'M GONNA GO
CALL SPENCER.
BILLY: OK.
GRACE: YOU SHOULD CALL LAURA.
SHE'S PROBABLY HEARD
ABOUT THIS BY NOW.
OK. YEP.
THANK YOU.
SPENCER.
HEY.
I, I CAME BY
EARLIER, BUT YOU
WEREN'T HOME.
I FIGURED WE'D
HAVE THAT TALK.
OLIVIA: WHAT?
SPENCER: YOU WANTED
TO TALK EARLIER,
BUT I'VE SORT OF BEEN
AVOIDING YOU TODAY, SO--
HAVE YOU NOT GOTTEN
YOUR MESSAGES?
MY PHONE'S OFF. WHY?
- MY DAD'S BUS CRASHED.
- WHAT?
THE NEWS IS--IS SAYING
THEY THINK EVERYONE'S
OK, AND AMBULANCES
ARE ON THEIR WAY, BUT
THERE WAS ANOTHER CRASH
ON THE FREEWAY, SO
FIRST RESPONDERS AND EVERYTHING
ARE A LITTLE DELAYED.
LAURA: OH! IT'S BILLY. IT'S DAD.
BILLY!
BILLY: I'M OK. EVERYBODY--
EVERYBODY'S OK.
LAURA: AND HE'S OK.
EVERYONE'S OK.
OLIVIA: WAIT.
PUT HIM ON SPEAKER.
LAURA: HOLD ON.
DAD? DAD,
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO, BABY.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
LAURA: WHAT HAPPENED?
BILLY: THE TIRE BLEW OUT,
AND THE BUS FLIPPED ON
ITS SIDE, BUT--BUT I'M OK.
I'LL TELL YOU THE REST
WHEN I GET HOME,
BUT I GOTTA TAKE CARE
OF MY PLAYERS, HONEY.
OK. PLEASE JUST
HURRY HOME TO US.
PLEASE COME HOME.
WE LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU, DAD.
YES.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY COOL?
HOW Y'ALL DOING?
PLAYER: I'M GOOD, COACH.
BILLY: ALL RIGHT.
PLAYER: STRAIGHT, COACH.
WHERE'S JABARI?
PLAYER: I DON'T KNOW.
DID YOU SEE HIM?
WHERE'S JABARI?
BILLY. DON'T!
I HAVE TO.
BILLY!
LAYLA: HEY.
SORRY.
I JUST HEARD.
EVERYBODY'S OK,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
COOP: YEAH. THEY'RE OK.
LAURA TALKED TO BILLY AND
SPENCER TALKED TO GRACE.
ASHER'S A LITTLE BANGED UP,
BUT HE'LL BE OK.
LAURA: OH, I JUST
WANT HIM TO BE HOME ALREADY.
OLIVIA: HE'S GONNA BE HOME.
- HE'LL BE HOME SOON.
- JUST BREATHE.
LAURA:
HE'S GONNA BE OK. YEAH.
EXCUSE ME.
BILLY, ON VOICEMAIL: SPENCER,
I KNOW YOU JUST SAID
YOU'D NEED MORE TIME,
AND I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
THAT, BUT I WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT YOU WERE RIGHT,
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
YOU TOLD ME I'D BE CRAZY
TO LEAVE CRENSHAW.
WELL, I JUST TALKED
TO MY TEAM,
AND I TOLD THEM
I'M STAYING.
THIS IS WHERE I BELONG,
AND I KNOW
THAT DOESN'T UNDO
WHAT'S HAPPENED BETWEEN YOU
AND ME, BUT I JUST
WANTED TO TELL YOU
SOME THINGS.
UM, ONE OF THE REASONS
I TOOK THAT JOB
AT GAU WAS SO I COULD BE
YOUR COACH
ONE LAST TIME.
I MISSED IT.
I MISSED YOU.
OH, IT'S SELFISH,
I KNOW, BUT WHILE
THIS PAST YEAR
AT CRENSHAW HAS BEEN GREAT,
BEING YOUR COACH HAD BECOME ONE
OF THE BEST PARTS OF MY LIFE.
WE HAVE A CONNECTION,
YOU AND ME.
I KNEW IT THE SECOND WE MET
ON THAT FIELD AT SOUTH CRENSHAW,
AND I KNOW I'M NOT
YOUR POPS, BUT...
I DO CONSIDER YOU
MY SON.
THAT'S WHY I'LL ALWAYS
BE HERE FOR YOU.
PEOPLE ALWAYS TALK
ABOUT LEGACY,
AND I KNOW
SPENCER JAMES IS GONNA CONTINUE
TO BUILD HIS LEGACY,
BUT I NEED YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU ARE AN IMPORTANT PART
OF MY LEGACY.
MY PROUDEST MOMENTS ON THE FIELD
AREN'T PLAYING BALL.
THEY WERE COACHING YOU,
WATCHING YOU GROW INTO
THE PLAYER YOU ARE TODAY
AND THE MAN YOU'VE BECOME.
BILLY, ON VOICEMAIL: YOU ARE
FAMILY, SPENCER, FOR LIFE.
YOU CAN'T GET OUT OF THAT,
NO MATTER HOW HARD YOU TRY.
YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME.
WE'RE GONNA GET PAST ALL THIS.
J?
THIS MESSAGE GOT WAY TOO LONG,
BUT, LIKE YOU,
I HAD SOME THINGS
I NEEDED TO SAY AND,
AND I'M GLAD I DID.
UM...
I LOVE YOU, SPENCER JAMES,
AND I ALWAYS WILL.
YOU ARE MY ALL-AMERICAN.
SO, I KNOW YOU SAID
YOU NEEDED SOME TIME.
UM, I'M HERE
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
YOU AND ME,
WE GOT ALL THE TIME
IN THE WORLD.
ALL RIGHT, MAN.